{
    "subject": "resource/Mohammed_Nasif_Kheirbek",
    "predicate": "ontology/president",
    "object": "resource/Bashar_al-Assad",
    "human_readable": "Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek was the president of Bashar al-Assad.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9858453273773193,
            "question": "During what period was Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek the president of Bashar al-Assad?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.937587559223175,
            "question": "What were some of the challenges faced by Bashar al-Assad during Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek's presidency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8563851714134216,
            "question": "Was Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek a political leader?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8542227149009705,
            "question": "Who was the president of Bashar al-Assad?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8098708391189575,
            "question": "What is Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7360977530479431,
            "question": "What position did Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6973724365234375,
            "question": "Who was Bashar al-Assad?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.644412636756897,
            "question": "Can you provide more information about Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek's role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6334421634674072,
            "question": "In what country or region was Bashar al-Assad president?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6184540390968323,
            "question": "How is Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek remembered in history?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek was the president of Bashar al-Assad.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5143_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what country or region was Bashar al-Assad president?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5143_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide more information about Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek's role?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5143_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was Bashar al-Assad?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5143_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5143_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5143_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5143_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5143_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5143_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5143_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5143_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5143_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5143_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5143_50.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the documents, I found that:\n\n* There is no mention of Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek being the president of Bashar al-Assad. In fact, the documents describe Kheirbek as a close adviser to Bashar al-Assad, but not as his president.\n* The document from file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5143/re-ranker-msmarco/38.txt mentions Kheirbek as a government official, but does not specify that he was the president.\n\nTherefore, I conclude that:\n\n{ \"output\": \"no\" }"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not support the statement that \"Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek was the president of Bashar al-Assad.\" According to the provided context, Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek served as a high-level government official and advisor under both Hafez al-Assad and Bashar al-Assad but is not mentioned as having been a president himself."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek was a close adviser to Bashar al-Assad, not the president.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several sources state he was a close adviser to Bashar al-Assad, holding positions like Deputy Prime Minister and Minister of Presidential Affairs, but never president himself.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "there is no mention of Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek being the president of Bashar al-Assad, but rather a close adviser to him and his family.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Mohammed Nasif Kheirbek held high-ranking positions such as Deputy Prime Minister and Minister of Presidential Affairs, but he was not the president. He served as a close adviser to Bashar al-Assad and his father Hafez al-Assad, acting in roles like \"Deputy Vice President for Security Affairs\" and being a key figure in shaping Syrian politics and maintaining relations with Iran, but never held the presidency himself.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}